978-995-8782 kkeller@umassd.edu



285 Old Westport Road North Dartmouth, MA 02747

Artist. Designer. Educator.

I am a student artist pursuing a career in art education who values the hard work and interpersonal skills required to lead a classroom in advanced artistic activities. I plan to collaborate with fellow artists and the community to generate meaningful experiences through art.

Education: GPA: 3.92

University of Massachusetts Dartmouth, Class of 2020 BFA in Art Education with a Concentration in Graphic Design Chancellor's List (2016-Present) 5-12 Visual Arts Teacher (Massachusetts License Pending) Chelmsford High School Class of 2016

Commonwealth Honors Scholar

## **Employment:**

Multiliteracy & Communications Center	Tutor (2019-Present) As an MCC tutor, I work one-on-one with students to guide their learning experiences with various class writing and presentation assignments.
New England Yachad	Staff Member (2019) Intern (2018) Yachad is a non-profit organization which works toward engagement and inclusion services for people with disabilities. With New England Yachad, I taught art classes, designed informational and branding materials, completed various administrative tasks, and most importantly, engaged with adults with a variety of disabilities.
America Reads	Tutor (2017-2018) As an America Reads tutor at Carney Academy, I assisted a first grade classroom with learning, classroom behavior, and interpersonal skills.
Bertucci's	Carry-Out Associate (2017) As a carry-out associate at a restaurant, I answered phones, packed orders, and engaged with customers to give them the best take-out dining experience possible.

## **Specialized Skills:**

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, HTML, CSS, Traditional Painting, Digital Painting, Drawing, Teaching, Curriculum Design, Research, Communication and Writing.

## **Leadership Activities:**

Ecaacisiiip /totivities:	
Honors Council UMass Dartmouth	Creative Specialist and
	Paint Night Leader
	(2018-Present)
	Secretary (2016-2018)
Yearbook	Cover Artist & Artistic
	Editor (2015-2016)
Junior Cotillion Mural	Designer and Co-Leader
	(2015)

## Awards:

Jennifer W. Mulnix University Honors Program Service Award (2019) Kyle Roy Scholarship (2019) Dante Vena Memorial Scholarship (2017) Chancellor Merit Scholarship (2016) Robello Art Scholarship (2016) Shirley Lavoie Memorial Art Scholarship of Chelmsford Art Society (2016) AP Scholar with Distinction (2016)

References: furnished upon request